[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Asian country was the Melonpan bread variety invented?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Vietnam", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hippos are related to cetaceans (whales and porpoises).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Admiral in the Imperial fleet takes control shortly after the beginning of the movie Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": "Piett", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozzel", "Ackbar", "Daala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first car model to sell one million cars in one year?", "correct_answer": "Chevy Impala", "incorrect_answers": ["Corvette", "Volkswagon Beetle", "Toyota Corolla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who voices the main computer on the Axiom in the movie WALL-E?", "correct_answer": "Sigourney Weaver", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrie Fisher", "Majel Barrett", "June Lockhart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did The Dirty Dozen star Jim Brown, the former football player?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The box turtle has a hinge on the bottom of its shell.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following primates is the closest related to humans?  (That is, this primate has more DNA in common with humans than any other living creature does.)", "correct_answer": "Chimpanzee", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemur", "Gorilla", "Orangutan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Boeing 747 project was bankrolled by the President of an airline company, when in 1965 a downpayment of $250,000,000 was made.  Which was the airline company?", "correct_answer": "Pan American", "incorrect_answers": ["American Airlines", "Delta", "United"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is considered the smallest mammal in length on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Kittis Hog-nosed Bat", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Pygmy Jerboa", "Etruscan Shrew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Skunks, which are omnivorous mammals, are one of the primary predators of these animals.", "correct_answer": "Honeybees", "incorrect_answers": ["Moles", "Termites", "Salamanders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the largest moon of Saturn and the second largest moon in the Solar System, which was the first satellite to be discovered after the discovery of the four Galilean moons?", "correct_answer": "Titan", "incorrect_answers": ["Io", "Rhea", "Triton"]}]